http://www.forfarathletic.co.uk/privacy-policy

Close
HomeLoons Lucky Lotto5050TicketsContactInformation
PlayersFixtures & ReportsFixture NewsMatch ReportsFixtures & ResultsLeague TableMatch DayFAFC ShopShop Now!TicketsSupporters ClubInformationNews And EventsSponsorshipMediaGalleryForfar Athletic TV
Policies
Website & Data Privacy Policy
Forfar Athletic Football Club Limited is committed to protecting the privacy of our website users.  In this policy we set how we will deal with your personal details.
Any information collected and stored, including cookies, will be of the following kind:
Your visits and use of our website
Information provided for the use of registering and/or subscribing to our website service
Contact details provided in the course of downloading information
Website Visits
We may collect information about your visits to our website such as IP address, location, browser type, referral source, length of visit and number of page views. This information may be used to improve our website's usability and for general marketing purposes. This data is not personally identifiable.
Cookies are used on this website
Some of the services we use such as Google Analytics, Clicky Analytics and addThis set cookies to allow us to gather anonymous data about your usage of our website.
A cookie is a text file sent by a web server to a web browser and stored in the browser.  The file is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page form the server.  This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser.
We may send a cookie which may be stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. The information we obtain from the cookie could be used to improve the website’s usability and for marketing purposes. We may also use that information to recognise your computer when you visit our website, and to personalise our website for you.
Browsers usually will allow you to refuse cookies but this could have a negative impact on the usability of many websites.
Using your personal data
Personal data submitted on this website could be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in any relevant parts of the website.
Our lawful bases for processing your personal data are: contract (e.g. for the purposes of providing a quote or requested information in order to do business with you) or consent (e.g. you provide your contact details in order to request information from us).
In addition to the uses already identified we may use your personal information to:
Improve your browsing experience by personalising the website.
Send marketing communications, if you have chosen to receive them.
Provide other companies with statistical information about our users; however, this information will not be used to identify an individual user.
We will not provide any personal information to a third party unless you have given your permission.
Marketing and your rights
You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes.  We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes of if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes.  You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by refusing your consent at the time of collection or at any other time by contacting us at This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it..
Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our members, advertisers and affiliates.  If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.
Other Disclosures
In addition to disclosures already discussed we may need to disclose the following information:
Where a country’s legal system requires us to disclose your personal information.
In connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings.
In order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk).
Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to third parties.
International data transfers
Information that we collect may be stored and processed by third party data processing companies to enable us to provide you with a suitable service. We only deal with reputable data processors and we are confident that your data is stored securely in accordance with data protection best practice.
If you are in the European Union, information which you provide may be transferred to and processed in countries which do not have data protection laws equivalent to those in force in the European Union. When you provide personal information, you expressly agree to such transfers.
Security of your personal data
We will take reasonable precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. Of course, data transmission over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet.
We will store all the personal information you provide on our secure servers or on third party secure servers. All electronic transactions you make to or receive from us will be encrypted.
Data retention
Data will only be retained for as long as is appropriate in accordance with financial and business requirements.
Policy amendments
We may occasionally update this privacy policy by posting a new version on our website. It is in your interest to check this page regularly to ensure you are comfortable with any changes made.
Third party websites
Our website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies of any third party websites.
Access to, retention and deletion of information – your rights
The Act gives you the right to request a copy of the information we hold about you.  Your right can be exercised in accordance with the Act and we have 30 days to respond.
You also have the right to ask us to erase, amend or limit the use of the data we hold about you.  If there is a legitimate and permissible reason why we cannot do this we will explain why.
We have a retention policy which means we do not keep information we hold about you for longer than necessary unless there is a legal obligation to do so.
Making a complaint
If for any reason you are not satisfied with our response, please make a formal complaint to Louise Taylor at This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
If you remain dissatisfied following his investigation and response then you can complain to the supervisory authority for data protection:
Information Commissioner’s Office
45 Melville Street
EDINBURGH
EH3 7HL                                                          (Telephone 0303 123 1115)
About Us
Club InfoContactClub Shop
Policies
Anti-Racism and Ethnic PolicyChild Wellbeing & Protection PolicyCode Of PracticeDisability PolicyGround RegulationsSocial Media PolicySupporters CharterUnacceptable Conduct
Site Info
Terms and ConditionsWebsite & Data Privacy Policy
Social Media
FacebookTwitterYoutubeInstagramFlickr
Our site uses cookies. If you're not happy about that please hit your back button.
© 2020 Forfar Athletic Football Club. All rights reserved.
This website, and its component parts, are the property of Forfar Athletic Football Club (unless otherwise stated), and are protected by the copyright laws of the United Kingdom and under international law. The website may not be copied, duplicated, stored or otherwise reproduced, in whole or in part or parts, without the express written consent of the Site Managers.
